[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "яблоко",
        "setName" : "english"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "orange",
        "back": "апельсин",
        "setName" : "english"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "driver",
        "back": "водитель",
        "setName" : "english"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "designer",
        "back": "дизайнер",
        "setName" : "english"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "bath",
        "back": "ванная",
        "setName" : "english"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "living room",
        "back": "зал",
        "setName" : "english"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "bed",
        "back": "спальня",
        "setName" : "english"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "tomato",
        "back": "помидор",
        "setName" : "english"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "ball",
        "back": "мяч",
        "setName" : "english"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "doll",
        "back": "кукла",
        "setName" : "english"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "p",
        "back": "абзац",
        "setName" : "tags"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "a",
        "back": "ссылка",
        "setName" : "tags"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "front": "img",
        "back": "картинка",
        "setName" : "tags"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "front": "border",
        "back": "рамка",
        "setName" : "css"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "front": "background",
        "back": "задний фон",
        "setName" : "css"
    }
]